{
    "subject": "resource/Hotel_Colorado",
    "predicate": "property/architecture",
    "object": "resource/Italianate_architecture",
    "human_readable": "The architecture of Hotel Colorado is Italianate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8318163752555847,
            "question": "Describe the architectural style of Hotel Colorado."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7885157465934753,
            "question": "What architectural style is the Hotel Colorado built in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.687553882598877,
            "question": "What are some common features of Italianate architecture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6566017866134644,
            "question": "Which country's architecture is reflected in the design of Hotel Colorado?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.584705650806427,
            "question": "How does the Hotel Colorado's architecture influence its appearance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45188623666763306,
            "question": "How does the Hotel Colorado's architecture contribute to its overall charm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4330313205718994,
            "question": "Why might someone choose an Italianate architectural style for a building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3870053291320801,
            "question": "Give an example of another building with an Italianate style."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36546948552131653,
            "question": "What are some historical examples of Italianate buildings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1995011270046234,
            "question": "Can you identify other hotels with similar architectural styles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The architecture of Hotel Colorado is Italianate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some historical examples of Italianate buildings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of another building with an Italianate style.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might someone choose an Italianate architectural style for a building?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2888_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the Hotel Colorado was modeled after the 16th Century Italian Renaissance Villa de Medici in Rome, and both hotels prominently feature red sandstone quarried in the Western U.S. on their exteriors. This supports the statement that the architecture of Hotel Colorado is Italianate."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the text states that both Hotel Colorado and The Brown Palace were built in the Italian Renaissance style, which was hugely popular for the design of grand, landmark buildings in the U.S. from the 1840s through the 1890s, but it does not specify that the architecture of Hotel Colorado is Italianate.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}